applevis.com 2014-11-22

# AppleVis Privacy Statement and Copyright Notice | AppleVis

### **General statement**

AppleVis fully respects your right to privacy, and will not collect any personal information about you on this website without your clear permission. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites. Any external links to other websites are clearly identifiable as such. Any personal information which you volunteer to AppleVis will be treated with the highest standards of security and confidentiality, strictly in accordance with the Data Protection Act's Privacy Statement.

### **Collection and use of personal information**

Apart from information that you volunteer to AppleVis either by emailing us or by filling the [online contact form](http://www.applevis.com/contact). AppleVis does not collect any personal data about you on this website. AppleVis does not make available any personal data about you to any third parties, unless obliged to disclose such information by a rule of law.  Any information that you provide is used by AppleVis solely for the purposes for which it is provided.

### **Collection and use of technical information**

The website of AppleVis does not use cookies, apart from temporary "session" cookies which enable a visitor’s web browser to remember which pages on this website have already been visited. Visitors can use this website with no loss of functionality if cookies are disabled from the web browser.

### **Copyright Notice**

© 2014 AppleVis, All rights reserved

Material on this website is protected by copyright. Any reproduction of material from this website must be requested and authorized in writing from AppleVis. Authorized reproduction of material must include all copyright and proprietary notices in the same form and manner as the original, and must not be modified in any way. Acknowledgement of the source of the material must also be included in all references.  AppleVis reserves the right to revoke such authorization at any time, and any such use must be discontinued immediately upon notice from AppleVis.
